let questions = [{"numb": 1, "question": "beliebegen", "answer": "any, yavudadaru", "options": ["any, yavudadaru", "unavoidable, \u0c85\u0ca8\u0cbf\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0caf", "lorry, track", "alleged, \u0cb9\u0cc7\u0cb3\u0cb2\u0cbe\u0c97\u0cbf\u0cb0\u0cc1\u0cb5,"]}, {"numb": 2, "question": "sitzgelegenheit", "answer": "seating accommondation", "options": ["seating accommondation", "beforehand", "under the waz, in transit", "massive sums"]}, {"numb": 3, "question": "Stellen", "answer": "places", "options": ["places", "simple, plane, \u0cb8\u0cb0\u0cb3", "Monthly average", "long distance"]}, {"numb": 4, "question": "g\u00fcnstigen", "answer": "cheapest", "options": ["cheapest", "additional", "bargain", "sofa"]}, {"numb": 5, "question": "Storm", "answer": "Electricity", "options": ["intervals, Gaps", "useless, vain, \u0cb5\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0ca5", "home", "Electricity"]}, {"numb": 6, "question": "unterwegs", "answer": "under the waz, in transit", "options": ["supposedly", "under the waz, in transit", "arm chair", "tempting, \u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cb2\u0ccb\u0cad\u0ca8\u0c97\u0cca\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0cb8\u0cc1\u0cb5"]}, {"numb": 7, "question": "gef\u00fcrchtet", "answer": "feared", "options": ["feared", "types", "careful", "stock market crashes"]}, {"numb": 8, "question": "hingeben", "answer": "whereas, however", "options": ["additional", "whereas, however", "arm chair", "however"]}, {"numb": 9, "question": "au\u00dfer", "answer": "except,beside", "options": ["Sick Notifications", "actually", "except,beside", "useless, vain, \u0cb5\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0ca5"]}, {"numb": 10, "question": "keinesfalls", "answer": "by no mean", "options": ["alleged, \u0cb9\u0cc7\u0cb3\u0cb2\u0cbe\u0c97\u0cbf\u0cb0\u0cc1\u0cb5,", "actually", "simple, plane, \u0cb8\u0cb0\u0cb3", "by no mean"]}, {"numb": 11, "question": "Zwangslaufig", "answer": "unavoidable, \u0c85\u0ca8\u0cbf\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0caf", "options": ["hence", "places", "applicant", "unavoidable, \u0c85\u0ca8\u0cbf\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0caf"]}, {"numb": 12, "question": "gegen\u00fcber", "answer": "towards, opposite", "options": ["except,beside", "arm chair", "simple, plane, \u0cb8\u0cb0\u0cb3", "towards, opposite"]}, {"numb": 13, "question": "Krankmeldungen", "answer": "Sick Notifications", "options": ["repeatedly, manytimes", "Sick Notifications", "except,beside", "places"]}, {"numb": 14, "question": "angeblichen", "answer": "alleged, \u0cb9\u0cc7\u0cb3\u0cb2\u0cbe\u0c97\u0cbf\u0cb0\u0cc1\u0cb5,", "options": ["sofa", "delays", "alleged, \u0cb9\u0cc7\u0cb3\u0cb2\u0cbe\u0c97\u0cbf\u0cb0\u0cc1\u0cb5,", "actually"]}, {"numb": 15, "question": "herk\u00f6mlichen", "answer": "usual, conventionally, SAAMANYAVAGI", "options": ["long distance", "intervals, Gaps", "seat row", "usual, conventionally, SAAMANYAVAGI"]}, {"numb": 16, "question": "konventionelle", "answer": "conventional", "options": ["conventional", "simple, plane, \u0cb8\u0cb0\u0cb3", "feared", "lower"]}, {"numb": 17, "question": "umsonst", "answer": "costless, free", "options": ["Bussiness tour", "costless, free", "usual, conventionally, SAAMANYAVAGI", "couple, pairs"]}, {"numb": 18, "question": "gem\u00fctlich", "answer": "comfortable", "options": ["Stranger, ODD, \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0c9a\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0cb0", "compulsarly", "comfortable", "types"]}, {"numb": 19, "question": "verlockenden", "answer": "tempting, \u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cb2\u0ccb\u0cad\u0ca8\u0c97\u0cca\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0cb8\u0cc1\u0cb5", "options": ["towards, opposite", "lower", "careful", "tempting, \u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cb2\u0ccb\u0cad\u0ca8\u0c97\u0cca\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0cb8\u0cc1\u0cb5"]}, {"numb": 20, "question": "Monatdurchschnitt", "answer": "Monthly average", "options": ["Monthly average", "careful", "beforehand", "costless, free"]}, {"numb": 21, "question": "Sessel", "answer": "arm chair", "options": ["already", "mainly, predominatly", "arm chair", "luxurious"]}, {"numb": 22, "question": "Gesh\u00e4ftreisen", "answer": "Bussiness tour", "options": ["comfortable", "useless, vain, \u0cb5\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0ca5", "actually", "Bussiness tour"]}, {"numb": 23, "question": "konkurrenz", "answer": "competition", "options": ["types", "seating accommondation", "competition", "alleged, \u0cb9\u0cc7\u0cb3\u0cb2\u0cbe\u0c97\u0cbf\u0cb0\u0cc1\u0cb5,"]}, {"numb": 24, "question": "tats\u00e4chlich", "answer": "actually", "options": ["actually", "sample", "couple, pairs", "previously"]}, {"numb": 25, "question": "Bewerber", "answer": "applicant", "options": ["beforehand", "prerequisites", "long distance", "applicant"]}, {"numb": 26, "question": "Fachterminus", "answer": "Technical term, \u0ca4\u0cbe\u0c82\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cbf\u0c95 \u0caa\u0ca6", "options": ["Technical term, \u0ca4\u0cbe\u0c82\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cbf\u0c95 \u0caa\u0ca6", "actually", "comfortable", "mainly, predominatly"]}, {"numb": 27, "question": "Langstreck", "answer": "long distance", "options": ["long distance", "towards, opposite", "package tour", "couple, pairs"]}, {"numb": 28, "question": "angeblich", "answer": "supposedly", "options": ["competition", "seat row", "couple, pairs", "supposedly"]}, {"numb": 29, "question": "Zeitverschiebung", "answer": "time lag, \u0cb8\u0cae\u0caf \u0cac\u0ca6\u0cb2\u0cbe\u0cb5\u0ca3\u0cc6", "options": ["Electricity", "useless, vain, \u0cb5\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0ca5", "also, likewise", "time lag, \u0cb8\u0cae\u0caf \u0cac\u0ca6\u0cb2\u0cbe\u0cb5\u0ca3\u0cc6"]}, {"numb": 30, "question": "niedrigen", "answer": "lower", "options": ["lower", "Additional cost", "massive sums", "time lag, \u0cb8\u0cae\u0caf \u0cac\u0ca6\u0cb2\u0cbe\u0cb5\u0ca3\u0cc6"]}, {"numb": 31, "question": "couch", "answer": "sofa", "options": ["sofa", "supposedly", "by no mean", "Stranger, ODD, \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0c9a\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0cb0"]}, {"numb": 32, "question": "verst\u00e4rke", "answer": "strengthen", "options": ["strengthen", "competition", "gaps", "additional"]}, {"numb": 33, "question": "zuvor", "answer": "previously", "options": ["careful", "tempting, \u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cb2\u0ccb\u0cad\u0ca8\u0c97\u0cca\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0cb8\u0cc1\u0cb5", "travel bussiness", "previously"]}, {"numb": 34, "question": "vergeblich", "answer": "useless, vain, \u0cb5\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0ca5", "options": ["also, likewise", "already", "costless, free", "useless, vain, \u0cb5\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0ca5"]}, {"numb": 35, "question": "voraussetzung", "answer": "prerequisites", "options": ["strengthen", "previously", "prerequisites", "couple, pairs"]}, {"numb": 36, "question": "vorsichtig", "answer": "careful", "options": ["usual, conventionally, SAAMANYAVAGI", "careful", "places", "whereas, however"]}, {"numb": 37, "question": "Versp\u00e4tungen", "answer": "delays", "options": ["luxurious", "delays", "Stranger, ODD, \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0c9a\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0cb0", "disposition, \u0c87\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0ca5"]}, {"numb": 38, "question": "zwangl\u00e4ufig", "answer": "compulsarly", "options": ["applicant", "types", "compulsarly", "by no mean"]}, {"numb": 39, "question": "enorme_summe", "answer": "massive sums", "options": ["mainly, predominatly", "useless, vain, \u0cb5\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0ca5", "hence", "massive sums"]}, {"numb": 40, "question": "Aufpreis", "answer": "Additional cost", "options": ["Sick Notifications", "lorry, track", "rather", "Additional cost"]}, {"numb": 41, "question": "zus\u00e4tzlich", "answer": "additional", "options": ["additional", "however", "mainly, predominatly", "whereas, however"]}, {"numb": 42, "question": "heim", "answer": "home", "options": ["home", "massive sums", "time lag, \u0cb8\u0cae\u0caf \u0cac\u0ca6\u0cb2\u0cbe\u0cb5\u0ca3\u0cc6", "intervals, Gaps"]}, {"numb": 43, "question": "luxuri\u00f6s", "answer": "luxurious", "options": ["Electricity", "intervals, Gaps", "luxurious", "crash accident"]}, {"numb": 44, "question": "\u00fcberwiegend", "answer": "mainly, predominatly", "options": ["intervals, Gaps", "massive sums", "competition", "mainly, predominatly"]}, {"numb": 45, "question": "mehrmals", "answer": "repeatedly, manytimes", "options": ["hence", "intervals, Gaps", "repeatedly, manytimes", "additional"]}, {"numb": 46, "question": "vorurteile", "answer": "biased, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0c97\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cb9\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1", "options": ["biased, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0c97\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cb9\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1", "intervals, Gaps", "package tour", "alleged, \u0cb9\u0cc7\u0cb3\u0cb2\u0cbe\u0c97\u0cbf\u0cb0\u0cc1\u0cb5,"]}, {"numb": 47, "question": "schlichte", "answer": "simple, plane, \u0cb8\u0cb0\u0cb3", "options": ["gaps", "conventional", "simple, plane, \u0cb8\u0cb0\u0cb3", "also, likewise"]}, {"numb": 48, "question": "Lastwagen", "answer": "lorry, track", "options": ["careful", "Sick Notifications", "lorry, track", "Stranger, ODD, \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0c9a\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0cb0"]}, {"numb": 49, "question": "Unglucksf\u00e4lle", "answer": "crash accident", "options": ["luxurious", "crash accident", "however", "sofa"]}, {"numb": 50, "question": "P\u00e4rchen", "answer": "couple, pairs", "options": ["couple, pairs", "comfortable", "compulsarly", "intervals, Gaps"]}, {"numb": 51, "question": "jedoch", "answer": "however", "options": ["however", "feared", "home", "actually"]}, {"numb": 52, "question": "Daher", "answer": "hence", "options": ["hence", "supposedly", "actually", "careful"]}, {"numb": 53, "question": "kostprobe", "answer": "sample", "options": ["Electricity", "sample", "Sick Notifications", "biased, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0c97\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cb9\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1"]}, {"numb": 54, "question": "vorab", "answer": "beforehand", "options": ["however", "beforehand", "bargain", "arm chair"]}, {"numb": 55, "question": "bereits", "answer": "already", "options": ["already", "home", "also, likewise", "comfortable"]}, {"numb": 56, "question": "pauschalreisen", "answer": "package tour", "options": ["except,beside", "useless, vain, \u0cb5\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0ca5", "package tour", "crash accident"]}, {"numb": 57, "question": "sitzreihe", "answer": "seat row", "options": ["Technical term, \u0ca4\u0cbe\u0c82\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cbf\u0c95 \u0caa\u0ca6", "intervals, Gaps", "seat row", "actually"]}, {"numb": 58, "question": "L\u00fccken", "answer": "gaps", "options": ["prerequisites", "Electricity", "lower", "gaps"]}, {"numb": 59, "question": "B\u00f6rsekrachl\u00f6ste", "answer": "stock market crashes", "options": ["explusion, uchhatane", "stock market crashes", "also, likewise", "under the waz, in transit"]}, {"numb": 60, "question": "Merkw\u00fcrdiger", "answer": "Stranger, ODD, \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0c9a\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0cb0", "options": ["package tour", "under the waz, in transit", "additional", "Stranger, ODD, \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0c9a\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0cb0"]}, {"numb": 61, "question": "Reiseveranstalter", "answer": "travel bussiness", "options": ["already", "Technical term, \u0ca4\u0cbe\u0c82\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cbf\u0c95 \u0caa\u0ca6", "any, yavudadaru", "travel bussiness"]}, {"numb": 62, "question": "Abst\u00e4nden", "answer": "intervals, Gaps", "options": ["Sick Notifications", "arm chair", "intervals, Gaps", "seat row"]}, {"numb": 63, "question": "Vertreibung", "answer": "explusion, uchhatane", "options": ["explusion, uchhatane", "Sick Notifications", "long distance", "massive sums"]}, {"numb": 64, "question": "ebenfalls", "answer": "also, likewise", "options": ["arm chair", "also, likewise", "previously", "sofa"]}, {"numb": 65, "question": "verf\u00fcgung", "answer": "disposition, \u0c87\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0ca5", "options": ["disposition, \u0c87\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0ca5", "beforehand", "seating accommondation", "by no mean"]}, {"numb": 66, "question": "schn\u00e4ppchen", "answer": "bargain", "options": ["however", "bargain", "careful", "disposition, \u0c87\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0ca5"]}, {"numb": 67, "question": "eher", "answer": "rather", "options": ["rather", "costless, free", "feared", "whereas, however"]}, {"numb": 68, "question": "wiederrum", "answer": "again", "options": ["again", "couple, pairs", "time lag, \u0cb8\u0cae\u0caf \u0cac\u0ca6\u0cb2\u0cbe\u0cb5\u0ca3\u0cc6", "prerequisites"]}, {"numb": 69, "question": "Genres", "answer": "types", "options": ["additional", "mainly, predominatly", "however", "types"]}];